Fajar Pratama Vishingah

I really like solving problems in programming implementation. It has its own happiness for me, but with my skills still not good, I will continue to learn. My experience is to create projects using full javascript, with node JS, Express JS, React JS, Next JS, React Native, Vue Js, Nuxt Js, and Mysql. Let's see my portfolio here.

Jl. Singgalang Blok Q No 8, Villa Pancoran Mas, Depok. - 16433

(+62) 85158822051

fajarrr035@gmail.com

Github

Linkedin

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Fazztech.id , Depok - Freelance

AUGUST 2022 - DESEMBER 2022

I am a Full-time Remote Project software engineer, working for a startup company whose scope of business activities is in the Fazztech 2022 Project Development sector. In this job request, in 3 months I developed 3 projects from the request of my team leader, every week I have a meeting with the team to discuss what I have developed, and fix existing bugs. Ensure the quality of the code in the merge request with a good code review. The projects that I have developed are Digiexpert Indonesia, Simentor - PUPR, and Fazztrack.

Service Phone, Depok - *Mobile Technician*, *Owner*

JULI 2017 - JANUARI 2020

Open hardware/software repair services, root android, unlock bootloader, custom rom, flash firmware, and from various types of mobile phones. In a day it can solve 10-15 devices with various damage to the device, such as broken LCD, bootloop, unable to recharge the battery, etc.

PT. Aplikasi Karya Anak Bangsa, Depok - Driver Online

JANUARI 2016 - JANUARI 2019

Deliver passengers to all areas of DKI safely and comfortably to their destination. deliver food to customers by prioritizing quality and safety, in a day can send more than 10 orders.

Planet Computer Sukabumi, Sukabumi - *Internship*

NOVEMBER 2010 - JUNI 2012

Perform computer assembly, software installation, operating system, In a day can receive computer assembly up to 5 - 10 computers, and receive damage to the customer's computer / laptop 10 devices, both software and hardware.

EDUCATION

Fazztrack Bootcamp, Online - Full Stack web developer

NOVEMBER 2021 - MARET 2022

On Fazztrack I learned a lot about soft skills and technical skills, I learned how to speak in public, how to speak in front of friends during a meeting for a project team, etc. Then I learned how to make a website application using full javascript. Then finally I can create multiple projects using Node JS, Express JS, React JS, Next JS, and React Native.

Digitalent Kominfo, Online - Junior web developer

AGUSTUS 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

In this digitalent training, I learned how to create an application website using PHP, learned how to create or design a database using MySQL, and other soft skills training such as English, how to speak in public, etc.

Universitas Gunadarma - System Computer

SEPTEMBER 2012 - NOVEMBER 2019

SMKT 1 Yaspida Sukabumi - Technical Information

MEI 2009 - APRIL 2012

PORTFOLIO

Vehicle Rental - (Express JS, MySQL, and React JS)

Full Stack

https://vehicle-react.netlify.app

Vehicle rental is a website for vehicle lending. This project was created in 3 weeks independently, by having a multi-user login feature, register, forgot password by email, add a vehicle (Owner), edit a vehicle (Owner), add a vehicle order transaction (User), edit profile and perform a vehicle search.

Vehicle Rental – Mobile - (Express JS, MySQL, and React Native)

Frontend

This project is a mobile version for the android platform. The creation of this project took 2 weeks for a front end with React Native, and the back end using a previous web vehicle rental project.

Raz Furniture - (Express JS, MySQL, and Next JS)

Frontend

https://raz-garlic.vercel.app

Raz Furniture is a project team, with 4 members (1 leader, 1 fullstack, 1 backend, and 1 frontend), responsible for the frontend and making the website display and implementation such as login, register, image picker, rendering conditions on the home page (Menu tabs).

Zwallet - (Express JS, MySQL, and Next JS)

Frontend

https://z-wallet-next-js.vercel.app

This project is an E-Money application, which can transfer money, as well as top up balances to various registered users. This project was built using the next js framework. Targeting 1 week in the process itself to build this front end project.

Coffee Shop - (Express JS, MySQL, and Next JS)

Frontend

https://violet-coffee-shop.netlify.app

Coffee Shop is a project team, with 5 members (2 backend, 2 frontend, and 1 leader). In this project, he is responsible for being the frontend and making the appearance of the website that has been provided from the mockup, and several implementations such as login, register, product menu, component rendering conditions, etc. that have adjusted the code style rules that have been formed in the project team.

DigiExpert Indonesia - (Nuxt JS)

Frontend

https://www.digiexpert.id

This project is a digital platform for collaboration of experts from Telkom Group, Alumni, BUMN and Professionals. In this project my team and I added a company feature, and my tasks here include slicing the admin dashboard, slicing and integrating the company feature, and some bug fixes for customization of the feature. This project uses the Nuxt JS framework.

SiMentor - PUPR - (React JS, Typescript)

Frontend

https://simentor.fazztech.id

This project is an application integrated with e-HRM that manages real-time data and information related to functional officials in the Ministry of Public Works and Public Housing. This project uses typescript, and my first experience using typescript, as well as using the React JS library. In this project I worked with the team to improve, improve in terms of appearance, and integrate functions in this project.

Fazztrack - (Nuxt JS)

Frontend

https://www.fazztrack.com

Fazztrack is a training program that is committed to producing professional developers and providing opportunities for careers in reputable companies. Fazztrack is a training program that is committed to producing professional developers and providing opportunities for careers in reputable companies. In this project, my team and I made improvements and improvements to the appearance, features, and additional features on the admin dashboard, and my job here is to improve the appearance and add features to the admin dashboard.